<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bit by Bit</title>
    <description>A simple blog of discoveries and failures.
</description>
    <link>https://bitassassin.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://bitassassin.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 06:42:18 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 06:42:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Website Undesign</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every single time that I build a new site, static or not, I am so grateful that I did not go into web design as a career. Even a site as simple as this, a blog, has, pretty much out of the box the most convoluted CSS imaginable. I even went with a theme that used a quite simple CSS layout…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, it is here now. This blog is yet another reboot of bit by bit, a blog I tried to start years ago on &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.getpelican.com/&quot;&gt;Pelican&lt;/a&gt;. Since then, I have tried &lt;a href=&quot;https://gohugo.io/&quot;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, and am now trying &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. I have yet to really find a static site generator that finds that balance between the fine control of hand-written HTML and the ease of use and visual splendor of a CMS. Here’s hoping that this time I will make more than one post before ignoring the blog for a year or two and starting over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bit by Bit itself is supposed to be a channel for me to describe projects I am currently failing at, with some salt sprinkled in. Topics I may end up discussing can range from mundane anecdotes about learning Javascript to the vagaries of chairing a nonprofit hackerspace. In the end, at the very least, it is an exercise in writing, and a break from the normal routine of work-sleep-work-hack-work-sleep-hack-work-sleep-work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are reading, neat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Bits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>https://bitassassin.github.io/webdev/update/2018/10/26/website-undesign.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bitassassin.github.io/webdev/update/2018/10/26/website-undesign.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>webdev</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
